<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyProcedure</string>
    <string name="plasma_pen_description">What is Plasma Pen? Plasma Pen is the most advanced, non-invasive skin tightening and rejuvenation device.  The Plasma Pen can be used in a number of procedures to enhance looks without the need for expensive and invasive surgery.  This plasma device has been perfected across thousands of treatments all over the world. This device will help you get a brighter, more contoured, and more youthful appearance.  Benefits of Plasma Pen Plasma Pen “fibroblastic” is highly versatile and is very effective in smoothing out wrinkles. tightening the eyelids, and can lift and rejuvenate any area of the skin.  Plasma Pen can: -Improve and brighten skin tone, laxity, and texture -Tighten loose skin -Dramatically reduce, inflate, and plump lines and wrinkles</string>
    <string name="microneedling_description">What is microneedling? Microneedling is one of the industry’s most promising skincare innovations, thanks to its minimal invasiveness and impressive versatility. By harnessing your skin’s power to heal itself, microneedling encourages the growth of new collagen for improved tone and texture. Over time, lines, wrinkles, and even some types of scars can fade significantly. Microneedling at West End Plastic Surgery in Washington D.C.  may become your new favorite skincare ritual.  How microneedling works to improve skin Microneedling is a deceptively simple procedure that can yield big results.  The microneedling tool looks a bit like a pen with extremely small, nearly microscopic, needles on one end. </string>
    <string name="prp_description">What is Platelet Rich Plasma? PRP (Platelet Rich Protein) is a natural product created from your own body. A small amount of blood is drawn from you and placed in a sterile tube that is spun down in a centrifuge to separate the different components of the blood. Red and white blood cells are divided from the platelets and the plasma (the clear fluid).  This plasma now contains a higher than normal number of platelets and is called platelet-rich protein.  Benefits of PRP Platelets are the cells in the blood that help tissue to heal and grow cells. The PRP Injected into specific areas of the skin, act as a matrix that promotes your own collagen to grow, regenerate tissue, and thus acts as to naturally smooth and tighten the skin. </string>
    <string name="botox_description">What Is BOTOX®? BOTOX® is a protein derived from botulinum toxin that is injected underneath skin in order to minimize or smooth out lines and wrinkles on the face.  When low doses of BOTOX® are used, it selectively weakens or relaxes facial muscles, giving the recipient a clean, smooth facial appearance.  Botox® Treatment Areas BOTOX® can be used on virtually any area of the body. Areas that are commonly treated include -Eyebrows -Forehead -Eyelids -Lips -Neck -Jawline -Breast areola after breast surgery. BOTOX® is also commonly used for excessive sweating (Hyperhidrosis), Bruxism (teeth grinding), reducing appearance of platysmal bands, calf reductions and \"gummy smiles.\"</string>
    <string name="ipl_description">What is it? Commonly called IPL or photo facial is used to address many skin concerns such as redness and hyperpigmentation with virtually no downtime. IPL uses light energy to reverse the visible signs of aging from general environmental wear and tear. It can also help stimulate collagen production reducing the appearance of fine lines and wrinkles. What are the Benefits of IPL Treatments? At West End Plastic Surgery, all of our non-surgical treatments seek to improve your skin.  IPL photofacials benefit your skin in two ways. First, these light treatments target your pigmentation problems such as age spots.  The darker cells absorb the IPL energy and the melanin pigment fragments.</string>
    <string name="question1">Do fillers hurt?</string>
    <string name="answer1">Depending on your individual pain tolerance, and where you’re using the filler, discomfort levels vary. We use a medical strength topical numbing agent to make all filler injections as comfortable as possible. Most people report little more than mild discomfort.</string>
    <string name="question2">How much does filler cost?</string>
    <string name="answer2">We carry a range of different fillers for different facial areas and concerns. Most people use at least one syringe, depending on the area being treated, and the thicker/longer-lasting the product is, the more expensive it is.</string>
    <string name="question3">How long until I see Botox results?</string>
    <string name="answer3">People receiving Dysport often see results in as little as 24 hours. Botox takes a little longer, between 24-72 hours to see first results. Full results can be observed at around fourteen days.</string>
    <string name="question4">How much Botox do i need?</string>
    <string name="answer4">Every face is different. A consult with our experienced Nurse Injector will allow us to accurately quote how many units you will need to achieve your desired result. There is no pressure to purchase anything at time of consultation.</string>
    <string name="question5">Will I be bruised or swollen?</string>
    <string name="answer5">Bruising and swelling are definite possibilities with any filler. We provide pre and post care instructions to you to minimize your chances of bruising as best we can. We will provide ice to you after your appointment to bring swelling down, and can advise natural supplements to aid in this process as well. Any swelling or bruising that does occur will normally resolve itself in one to two weeks. We encourage you to follow up with us if you have any concerns.</string>
    <string name="question6">Is filler reversible?</string>
    <string name="answer6">Most of the fillers we offer are Hyaluronic Acid-based fillers, which are reversible. In the unlikely event you want to dissolve some of your filler, this can be done in-office during a short visit.</string>
</resources>